all right let's see what we've got what
do you remember from the first time we
met the first time we met was at my
college at least and I was setting up
chairs and I think he thought I was a
janitor I was wearing sweat pants and
was not prepared to set up your life
presence out of my life or meet you and
I wasn't really interested in meeting
anyone and kind of just went from there
all I really remember was talking about
Taylor Swift and talking about how guys
love when the bass drops in that song
that sounded like the goats I knew you
were trouble yeah that's really all I
remember from the first time that we
read I remember the next time we met a
little bit better heard a real first
song that I talked about but a good
first impression
okay first impression what do you
remember about the first time we met I
think probably about the same as you I
mean I didn't I certainly don't think
either of us wanted to have any
expectation of meeting somebody you
liked in a romantic way but I remember
being happy I was there because there
was a blizzard outside nothing one shows
to happen and this meeting I'm talking
to you before the show I thought you're
cool but I kind of dismissed it as like
well that's something that I'm not going
to meet again don't use nice I think
that's the truth you know I don't think
they either of us really thought we
would encounter each other all this all
this business
okay list your top three memories we've
had together well I mean I would say
probably the obvious one is us getting
engaged but I want to work I would say
the first would be spending that whole
first weekend together the week after we
met because that was kind of where it
went from like oh here's this person I
was I didn't think I was gonna be ever
again - all of a sudden now we're
hanging out we have this chemistry and
this is really exciting but I think even
leaving that weekend neither of us
really knew what was going to happen but
it was the first time in a long time
that I was like really excited about
something I think well the third one is
the engagement which I'll get to I think
number two is probably it's probably
gonna grafting with you the first summer
we were together when we I had never
gone away water rafting I was very
nervous about that yeah very very
nervous I had all sorts of visions of me
getting my head against a rocket and
that being the end of it but that was
one of those times where I just felt
like we've been a that's like maybe like
three or four months at that point and
then
that was the first time that I realized
how much fun I had with you all the time
and also how adept a ten year old kid is
at setting up the tents conveyances
leaving a basically flat intent for the
first night but the third the third and
most important one is definitely us
getting engaged because I thought the
weirdest part to me still is that I
thought you knew what was coming because
we had talked about like what kind of
ring do you want like this is something
that's somewhat imminent and might
happen and then when we're going up to
your parents house that morning and you
specifically said offhandedly like don't
ever surprise me with the proposal
because I was making fun of you for
always watching the end of reality shows
before you watch the beginning because
you don't get to attach the characters
that I kind of threw me up and then the
longest day that I've ever experienced
continued where it was ten hours of me
literally not listening to anything you
were saying but the fact that it took me
taking a ring out and your entire family
knowing what's going on before you
realized and then you swearing in front
of your grandmother I don't know if I
can swear here but it was great all
right
you could swear by the way okay well in
that case she said holy fuck in front of
her 86 year old grandmother was
phenomenal I don't think you a bad news
[Music]
all right well this how that goes right
into that why did you want to marry me
there are a lot of reasons I wanted to
marry you I think that one of the main
reasons that I wanted to marry you and
still want to marry or because we get
along so seamlessly I think that when we
talk about it and when people ask us you
know what you argue about it or what you
know what do you guys talk about theater
why do you guys get along or really just
any of those reasons there are so many
things and so many reasons that we
shouldn't be together it's so many
things that shouldn't have brought us
together and so many things that like
should have happened to push us apart
yeah it'll be the long distance for a
year and a half and I was still in
college I mean that and we could have
broken up so many times in there and
thanks for really hard for so long but
like through all of that time and not to
say that things weren't hard and like
there were probably times that we both
questions whether or not we're making
the right decision but like through all
of that and just seems so clear at the
end of it that you're the person that I
was supposed to be with it and it was
crazy because moving down to New York
didn't even seem like a big deal like
moving from me into New York it was like
no big deal
moving in together
I mean it's so minted leading up to it
but actually once we once that happen
you know yeah but now that we live
together it's like no big deal well it
was like we move in together and nothing
changed right I didn't even notice it
almost right well no but I think I feel
like the only struggles we ever had were
due to outside factors like any time
yeah you and I being together was always
really easy yeah I also think that the
fact that we just wanted to seed a
little more and didn't have the ability
to I think so makes us appreciate each
other more now and I think of whatever
if we had just started dating and we
lived in the same city and moved in
after two months of some people did I
also I think that right from the
beginning one of the biggest things
about you is I've had such an inherent
level of trust in you I've never ever
damaged you like ever I have always
known that no matter what I could always
know that you've had my back
like most people and long-distance
relationships would not be able to be
like oh yeah well that's my boyfriend
this median through Charles around to
different colleges where he also met me
College Sutan where he also met me at a
party you know and all of a sudden like
how are you supposed to trust him like
that but just it was almost unspoken
that we just inherently trusted each
other and having that right from the
beginning was so important I think both
of us growing together and obviously you
know that's core and communication is
cooler listening his car yeah anytime
your long-distance and you if you don't
have trust in that situation you're done
that's what I wanna marry you
how do you describe me to others I don't
know that it comes up that much I feel
like that's a weird thing to say but
like in that direct of a form it like I
guess I'm thinking of how well when I
first described you to my parents
let's start with that because I think
because of the fact that there was the
age difference and not even that eight
times but four and a half years which is
not a big deal
in the grand scheme of things but the
fact that you were at college at the
time I think when I would describe you
of people especially early on it would
be me having to like justify it and
probably you to the same extent of like
are you dating this touring example
meaningful lives in New York but when I
told my parents that I the you and I
were dating and that you were still in
college I think they immediately judged
well what kind of person you were which
I understand because a lot of 21 year
old college girls are not the most
mature people in the world I don't think
a lot of people in college are but the
thing I was stressed was that it never I
heard I had to remind myself and I self
remind remind yourself how young you are
relatively because I've never gotten
that vibe from you like I feel like in a
lot of ways you're a lot more mature
than I am a lot more mature than a lot
of people in their 40s and that's either
your personality or just a combination
your personality and the fact that
you've had to kind of be the adult a lot
of situations with your family and stuff
growing up and that
and I feel like you've always had to
take a lot of responsibility and
therefore you didn't have the luxury of
like goofing around but yeah I mean I
think that was kind of the way I
conveyed to my parents to let them know
like I'm not something like creep and
she's not so maybe it and what I told
them well I told my friends about you it
was just I think the thing that I said
that most often was that it just like it
felt different and I hadn't felt that
way about anybody in a long time and
then and then ever you know maybe like
as things progressed it was clear to me
that what you and I had going out was
something that I hadn't had with anybody
else and I think you always are
comparing it a relationship to whatever
the best relationship you think you had
in the past was and then all of sudden
that surpasses it and you're like oh I
guess I don't have to be hung up on that
anymore so yeah I think just as somebody
who's kind didn't mature and someone who
I have what is similar and different so
similar I definitely say that in a lot
of ways were on you know the same
wavelength when it comes to you know
what we care about how we sort of like
approach life like pretty even-keeled
people you know don't like to go out too
much which I also like value you
obviously got a 92 but that's certainly
a job but you know I think that we have
the same approach to a lot of different
issues and you know we don't we're just
kind of calm people I like that about us
I don't really know how I mean I don't
know how we're different that's probably
something I should well I mean not
necessarily
we certainly are a lot more similar than
we are different obviously our lives are
incredibly different but yeah well
that's kind of like the biggest thing I
mean obviously I work all day so that
would probably be a person I mean that's
the thing because it's one thing to tell
people like why you're interested in
somebody but the first time you you see
something with that person I think tells
you a lot and to me I've always had a
good feel for that like when I see my
friends with the new grill of their date
like whether or not it's probably going
to work out and I think when people saw
us together that was the comment that we
got more than anything else was like it
seems like you two were just like locked
in in terms of just being on the same
wavelength in terms of not not only like
sense of humor and personality but just
basically had a person I am the fact
that I'm sarcastic and I like to make
references to obscure things a lot of
people were their friends their
girlfriends or anybody felt kind of
alone for the rock that we know that
I'll talk about but I feel like you and
I both kind of bounce off each other and
I mean we are kind of like a comedy duo
amongst our friends in a way of just
like something that we can work towards
yeah I think about Stephanie a big
differences you know the day job paint
job
well and also what like I think here's
somebody who and obviously we've talked
about it before like you're much more
oriented towards small town than a city
house over the park of the yard or not a
car and I think that's a byproduct the
way you grew up but you know that's
something that you've been willing to
compromise for the time being but I
think that in terms of like what we
value obviously the things that matter
in terms of family and what we believe
in a line but in terms of what be like
where we envision ourselves living at
that kind of thing I think that's
probably been one of the only sources of
my car yeah we'll deal with it another
day or ten years or five years or three
years when we move back to me why are
you hesitant to tell me
I mean I think we're pretty open with
each other about most things I think
sometimes I'm hesitant to tell you like
what my fears are regarding my future
and as a result our future like then you
self doubt that I have regarding my
chosen career or whether or not I think
everything's in the pan now they try to
I kind of try to keep that to myself as
I know earlier I was I feel like I was a
lot more negative that I have now about
how things were going for me and I think
that affected our relationship the times
of me letting that negativity or not
being able to separate like I feel
shitty about the show that I've just did
so I'm gonna bring that over again for
the conversation that I have with you so
I think I try to kind of tamper that
down when I'm able to and I don't I
don't feel that way as much anymore but
there are times where I feel like I'm
gonna sulk and I just kind of do that on
my own on the train that I kind of let
it go that's how I get sacks well but
it's not you know I think if there's any
this situation where I'm upset I mean it
just happened this weekend where I feel
like I sure didn't go well like I'll
always talk to you about that because I
know not only that you're gonna listen
to me but you're gonna make me feel
better about it but I also don't want to
argue with that because I work in a
field where there's a lot of rejection
and negativity I did that every time I
was upset about something you guys
really
wimp so I don't know I mean in terms of
other stuff that I have medicine to tell
you lay it all out there I don't know I
mean I think we've we've gone out of our
way to talk about like people we've
dated and past relationships and that
sort of thing because I think it really
matters anymore like I know I feel like
neither of us were really coming out
like oh I just don't wanna hear about
anybody that you've been with this I
feel like it's a little unhealthy
honestly when people have this weird
mindset of like oh well we're together
now so let's pretend that neither of us
have ever been with anybody else before
if anything I think that's probably not
really the best approach but I don't
know I think we're pretty forthcoming
with each other are there things that
you like actively keep from me I mean I
think it goes to what we were saying
before about the difference in this
where it's like every time I feel like
oh okay homesickness to move back out of
the city or like every time I hear a
freaking car horn like can I just move
back to a place that doesn't have car
horns or you know a place where people
aren't yelling at each other all the
time or you don't have to take the
subway we'll don't sit on top of you or
stink all the time like lips or nose
clip their nails a public place like not
a lot of that mean there isn't and you
know when I think about raising a fan
getting married a lot of like my fears
around raising a family in the city come
up but I feel like where you don't tell
me all the time when you have a bad name
to show when I think about our future
together in New York I get really
nervous about living here forever yeah
when we talk about buying a place in New
York like wow that seems like an awesome
idea it also seems like tying us really
really deeply to New York and while
we're young that's awesome and it also
it's such a tough thing because you're
so tied to here with your job and I
could literally be anywhere as long as I
have my computer like I could literally
anywhere and that's what makes it so
tough to feel like I can always be like
you know super honest about where would
be or you know how I totally see my
future with well I feel like even if we
don't say it in specific terms we both
kind of have an understanding and an
agreement that like this is where I need
to be now and this is where we're
probably going to be for the foreseeable
future whether that's three years for
five years or seven years but that we
both agree that we don't want to raise
kids here and like live here forever but
I also know that that's tough when
there's not a like it I wish that there
were a scenario where I could say it's
going to take me five years to
accomplish XYZ that
anywhere and I'll just fly over
everybody even that sort of thing but
you know we know the best reality
situation I guess that's why how's it
Asami
yeah alright what privileges do you
think well recently but other than being
me is generally generally like what to
take for granted I mean just I guess
within I feel like I'm talking about
like comedy specifically but you know I
get really frustrated with going to your
shows mostly because I get frustrated
with many comedy specifically and I
think that if we're talking like this I
think I think that you erased me to
family where you were brought up to be
very conscious and conscientious person
about gender and your sister and mother
and father are very smart people who I
think are very aware of the way they
raised you to drew people home I go to
shows I get really frustrated because I
see a lot of like 95% guys and then
you're out of the show as always like
the girl talking about like the period
jokes and her moves and so it's been
tough for me to like go your shows
because I then complain to you after
about like the discrepancies in comedy
where it's like all you know 150 men
doing this and then one woman doing this
and then it's like why because just
numbers-wise it's a tie or side to man
versus and then I mean that's how for
you just to say we like travel on your
own
yeah but I don't know I don't think you
specifically take a lot of things for
granted I don't know you don't really
walk around like some man's shirt man
you know like there's some guys just on
one of this and you know exactly who I'm
talking about the way I'm talking about
these has to be well because I I could
not be engaged to someone who was this
stereotypical tango guy who was the rich
leave information maybe just a person of
certain race of a certain class who
works a certain job with warship types
of gloves that fins or a really certain
stereotype person yeah yeah and you
don't exert yourself like that
yeah good
that's your earliest political memory I
mean I think the first thing that I
really remember being aware of was the
Lewinsky thing because I was like 10 and
that was all anybody talked about for a
year and so I don't think it was ever
really explained to me what that like
what exactly was going on absolutely
never enough that my parents didn't
really feel like tackling the oral sex
is there anything oral sex conversation
I don't think that happens with kissing
parents
conversation yeah so I don't know that
you know because it's hard to really be
politically aware as a little kid other
than like knowing that important things
happen in the world like I remember when
the Oklahoma City bombing things like
that that's more world something in
politics but yeah Clinton is the first
president that I remember distinctly and
we you know my parents were both
Democrats and so they liked Clinton but
they're also fairly I think wasn't prude
but they're pretty traditional and so
one thing with what was he happy I think
they were very this
like well he's just confirming what
we've all thought about politics for you
know all the time basically this even
before that you kind of got the vibe
from him then he was this like very
slick talking kind of like smarmy guy
who he knew he was very meticulous with
how he was talking to people and
somebody pulling on running so it was
hard going to the 90s was nice because
everything was going so well you know
but I feel like I've said this to you
before I think the nineties were like
our version of the 50s it was this time
that everybody was back on now like I
say the best time I heard was making
those money and it was the best choice
and there's always a and weird feeling
around nostalgia when you grow up yeah I
think politically that's the first thing
that I really remember and then
obviously the defining moment of my
childhood is 9/11 which I mean it's hard
to not enter to find out of politics I
mean that was my fourth day of high
school and I lived in New Jersey so
there were people who knew people who
were there and I think that's the first
time I really like took an interest in
what was going out of the world because
you couldn't ignore it anymore
like I still remember the day after that
happened when we were in homeroom and
they had us do the Pledge of Allegiance
and nobody could get through it like it
makes me choked up now think about this
is something you've recited since you
were five without ever thinking about
the context of it and then all of a
sudden that we got this different
meaning so yeah I think that probably is
the whiskey thing and then obviously
the world change living how do you think
I was influenced by growing up as a
first-generation American and what would
you change
I don't that means what what I change is
that for me maybe I'm s to myself doing
it well well how do you think I was I
was influenced by growing I was the
first generation in America well I think
that one of the interesting things about
talking to your dad and listening to him
and just sort of watching him obviously
you know me I know most of my life like
observing people and if I can do mostly
observing and less talking I'm a happier
person but watching your dad he's a
really fascinating guy he's always
thinking about ways that he can better
himself save money and help you guys and
I think those are three qualities that
you have taken in and that he's not your
mom as well and I think that we're gonna
happen potentially in the hallway family
like I did yeah not that my parents
didn't instill some of those qualities
but thinking about money and the ways
that he does not you know a thing
we think about like if my mom wants to
buy something it's like did it let's
imagine I absolutely machine buy better
polar opposites in terms of you know she
doesn't really think about what she's
spending her what she's spending it on
whereas my dad completely invest you
know when you grow up with nothing I see
then you go one of two directions you
either over adult everybody and buy all
the things that you wish you could have
had or you go in his direction which is
being so overly frugal that you can't
even fully enjoy the money that you've
made and it kind of I mean he's occupied
like he's what almost six years old and
I don't think a day goes by where he
doesn't think about money in some
capacity and it's because of growing up
that way and I feel badly for him
sometimes because he's done such amazing
things for himself in America and he has
a very comfortable life but I don't know
that he ever can fully appreciate that
yeah but I think not that you're not
appreciative of what you have but when
you have a dad like I do who came from
nothing in other stands what it means to
like kind of place yourself up by the
bootstraps I think that's been a good
example for me in terms of not taking
comfort for granted necessarily after I
do but just knowing what he went through
it kind of is a motivating factor to not
be lazy
yeah
how do you think my political views have
affected my relationship with my family
well I I perceive you as somebody who
you agree with me on those things in
terms of life
ideologically you know you think there
should be probably more control over
your choice that's like the world I have
a lot of important issues but I think
that you are more disillusioned with
politics that I am like I'm more
inclined to get behind somebody like
Obama or that sort of thing we're in
it's going well they're all kind of
crappy what do you think that's an
accurate thing to say I mean I don't
know if I'd go that far to say they're
all kind of crappy but but then I think
you're I think you have it sometimes you
get frustrated with just how the system
is I get frustrated with media
portrayals generally of all politics
regardless of party like I get
frustrated with the fact that you know
Hillary Clinton wait and Jeb Bush sad
today are things that people well in
terms of your relationship with your
family I think because of the fact that
your mom is so like super right wing you
have had to make a conscious decision as
a SMI especially to just let a lot of
stuff kind of let a lot of stuff go
because it's not worth having the
argument or saying what are you talking
about that's not true when you know that
you not necessarily changed somebody's
viewpoint because I think I mean I don't
know is your dad is he registered as a
Republican I think actually like my dad
may be even more Republican than my mom
just not a cycle
last focus like my mom was willing to
engage and just all our screaming
matches as we both yeah well know about
her beliefs luckily this past year she's
told that a little bit down from some of
the viewpoints that she's had but if you
get dad talking he's pretty right-wing
in a lot of his viewpoints you know and
especially this way or this way and you
know on the moral side of things as well
but I think technically a might even a
registered Republican because when I was
able to register to vote my parents told
me that was all the only choice that I
had was to register you know as I didn't
know that you didn't have to I really
didn't like so I got to the place where
you go to vote to go vote for Obama and
I like in the product brother you were
in either and I didn't realize that you
couldn't vote for anyone in the front so
that was a little bit of a black down to
kind of like I feel like you whatever
opinions your parents have you've been
able to separate that from forming your
own opinions well luckily I mean I went
to after high school because going to a
Catholic High School you have so many
viewpoints pushed on to your entire life
you know if you go to a Catholic Mass
every single Wednesday and you would
amass on Sunday then you have people
telling you exactly what you need to do
then you have the bishop coming and
saying hey
came from an anti-gay marriage
commercial isn't that great like you
just grow up with these viewpoints
shoved in your face and so when I went
to college I had anthropology I had
gender studies I had I mean liberal arts
college yeah there were so many other
options
and so I guess I took the opposite route
and said I'm just going to do it exactly
against everything that I've been told
to do and try to just learn everything I
possibly can about what else exists not
follow everything I've been told to
learn and just go the opposite way
you think that has more to do with kind
of rebelling against the education that
you had whether climate that were more
about your parents or I think it has to
do with me wanting to hope that more
exists than what people are saying
because their viewpoints yeah it'd be so
sad for me if all that existed was what
people sat on base so if all that
existed was like nope any people are
back down and story like that right and
like that's all people learned growing
up so I think that was my goal of in
going to college was only take classes
that were like absolutely I took classes
and
I take classes and moods at my tech
classes like in every single other
religion that Catholicism just because I
did not want to learn anything that I
had learned before she was really mad
mad that you were learning that for me
to learn things that she didn't think
were useful in any way wasn't what she
thought they were useful as she didn't
want you taking class about Islam or
this or that but also that like when I
told them I was getting a degree in
gender studies that was like the world
was ending like how could I was spending
almost a quarter million dollars on a
college education where I would never in
a million years get a job or be thought
of as an intelligent person right like
I'm not a lawyer a doctor I'm not like
going to run the world because I can
only think about culture like oh god
yeah when you but when it comes up like
now now with your parents obviously but
someone says I go what you majored in
college I saw big laughter I got laughs
yeah so what do you feel like you have
to explain yourself yes no I remember
that but somebody today said oh that
makes my politics degree sound like I'm
a genius and I was like I'm at work oh
yeah thinking I had your dick but in
real life I was like I probably know a
lot more about culture race religion and
how to talk about them in a way that
doesn't piss people off but also isn't
to PC yeah so like you can really just
go somewhere else like it doesn't matter
yeah that's a little off topic but I
think that that way of being able to
shape how I talk about things too and
walk that really fine line between
pissing my mom off angry my dad and
still believing in what I want to
believe in has been a
Yeah right I think the biggest bail for
you or anybody who majors in gender
studies as a woman is for people to not
just assume you're someone like raving
feminist two things all men are equal
because I think that's not to see what
people think about gender studies well I
think that's what that questionnaire I
felt like you know I don't you know I
don't think that there's necessarily
like a set person and I think that I
walked into a lot of stereotypes when I
was in college to playing hockey being
Gender Studies major being for main you
know just being athletic in general you
know there's a lot of different
stereotypes about you like - so are you
concerned that I won't be able to
provide health care for the family my
job which is a good thing because I
didn't yeah yeah well luckily I work for
employee benefits company so the
benefits are actually a great so I don't
actually think in today's world that
really matters who's you know getting
the we talk about this it's like we kind
of make high five that if one year
you're making a ton of money then that's
awesome if the next year I'm making in
time I need that's awesome yeah if it's
because I have a full-time job we're
getting covered with healthcare that's
awesome so no I'm not worried good I'll
provide
how do you think that political system
has failed us you or me well I think
there's so little bipartisanship that
it's just I mean I was saying bias that
somebody who's an Obama supporter but
the amount that the Republican Senate
has blocked everything that he's trying
to do even at the expense of benefiting
the American people just to promote a
certain agenda it's really troubling to
me so you know I think I'm not
necessarily somebody who has any
delusions that one president is going to
make everything great one person is
gonna make everything horrible but I
think there's so much bickering at this
point that there's not really a lot
that's been accomplished I don't really
know how how that changes obviously I
don't know what do you think I
definitely have to agree with you as
Steven reading daily even with the
Supreme Court being at a floor floor
traveling without holding things up they
were I was reading that with them at
tides turning into that said that
nothing will pass technicality and well
every other moment suggests will be shot
down yeah ice that bipartisanship is
really what and here's me a lot like
that so there's a lot of awesome you
know people from me like Olympia Snowe
who you know left politics because of
bipartisanship like it was so angering
that she would she left and she was in I
think for 18 years and
and it's women like that but I think
politics needs and I think when people
get so mired with AI Republic and I need
to believe this and I'm a Democrat I
need to believe this and you can't see
anywhere in the mill thousand it's so
dangerous like and people aren't even
willing to say I call somewhere in the
middle because there's no candidate
that's all smart right yeah I think well
that's why I'm gonna do it on these two
and Leno or whatever we're they would
literally read people quotes from the
other candidates and attributed to you
know some of those like Obama versus
McCain they say like well Barack Obama
said blah blah blah even if it was
McCain club and the person would be like
oh no that's ridiculous even if they
said they were McCain supporter you know
anything like people they all they it's
a very black and white and I think that
I mean that's why I think you've so
similar quizzes up saying like just what
are the issue that you care about and
what do you believe and then we're going
to tell you who your most aligned with
politically and so that way you're not
just saying oh well I agree with that
because it's Hillary and I think that's
ridiculous because Ted Cruz even though
I probably would be saying hey Lenny why
do you think people are so ill-informed
or missing Park develop so much like why
you think those like hey what do you
think about this like those always do so
well on the streets that was a dumb
people yeah yeah like I was reading
today like people were saying oh I'm so
upset that my federal income tax is so
high with like forty four percent of
people don't you pay federal income tax
yeah like you're upset and fifty six
percent
that's you know well in a year and over
now of comments sections being the way
people communicate it's just a sound
ring also a lot outraged about something
people really don't know three people
like it and so all of a sudden gives you
this ego boost
three people support your idiotic claims
and so all of a sudden you're on your
massive soapbox with your political
beliefs so I just think it's dangerous
when people get out of it those tanks
and riots
yeah I think that I mean to your right
there there's no most interesting and I
don't know I guess is putting in more
people than on politicians themselves
but when people have that mindset of
like well this is a party online with so
everything they say is the gospel and no
logic from the other side will even
enter my brain I think that's that could
be kind of dangerous so sort of office
is on there but with I think a lot of
the theme of this election with Bernie
Sanders itself is great you know how
super PACs and a lot of money has been a
driving force like do you think that has
been well people have talked about what
if they disallowed that from happening
what if they said you cannot take that
kind of money everything has to be
funded based on like you all have
essentially the same allotment for your
campaign it's the same way that you know
when you lost an Oh Jay show it wasn't
the problem was that the legal system is
unfair when one person can have a lawyer
that there
the other person has a public defender
it's not going to be fair so of course
in politics that give somebody who has a
ton of support financially from super
PACs and from all these supporters right
you're it's going to be very hard to
compete with that
for examines trying to use that to his
advantage saying like look I'm not like
everybody else in taking all these
handouts I'm raising money getting small
donations on but yeah I think it would I
think it would probably be better and
obviously even people who get a lot of
money I think it would be a lot less
stressful for them also so they could
focus on the things that you care about
rather than trying to curry favor from a
bunch of people who have deep pockets
that's one of what scares you the most
these days I think the fact we talk
about this but what scares me the most
is the direction of this country is
heading in without a true and clear
definition of where the leadership is
going you know and people are saying
yeah it's going to be Hillary and Trump
at the end and that's you know find her
the people who believe in both but
that's still a little scary for me and I
think that having an unclear path and
such a bipartisan druing and also it's
really scary that Trump has made it this
far that's what really scares me it
scares me that so many people in this
nation can believe in a guy like that
but at least we live in a place where
there is the checks and balances you
know anything he's not going to be
Korean from yeah but I guess the thing
about it that I cover in violence
is was my life significantly different
when george w bush was president versus
when Obama was president but I think it
would be different if Travis Rosen
probably because I I think that we can
look back in 50 years
don't forget cruising he's almost I'm
gonna try to reverse a lot of things but
I think that we'll look back in 50 or
100 years people could agree with this
or not disagree with this turnout but
fifty or hundred years Bush and Obama I
think will be looked up in history books
as you know good press hence yeah but I
think that if Trump was president it
would be a disaster yeah it would be a
worldwide disaster it's just kind of
like a mockery and that's so scary
yeah because when you when you hear
about plans or attempts at plans like
destroying the Middle East building wall
but that is scary
how do you bring a child into the world
with things like that being said with
the quote where he said if I don't win
I'm not threatening violence but it may
happen like notice yeah he's a time
Cleveland like right that's a real thing
that you say and he's like taunting
these white people to say like let's go
be violent against people that don't
vote for us that's insane that's a very
dangerous world that we are living like
that's not I mean I think but again I
think whoever whoever's in charge think
that's scary now it's just the capacity
for like random acts of mass violence
until that will be terrorism it can be
like in terms of
but the fact that you can have seemingly
a safe plan for your day where I'm going
to get up and take a shower or go to the
movies and you could get shot there like
that's not how it always was so that but
I also think that on the other side that
you can't just live your life and that's
what we always try setting them on like
what I'm gonna talk about living in New
York you can't live your life not riding
the drink and you can't live your life
not going to work you can't live your
life afraid of absolutely everything
because anything could happen
how do you function they're just yeah
you'd be crippled is their life so what
issues do you wish I cared about more
and why I think you do really that's
like a Syria you lack the like you
really do well that's not yeah okay I
think I feel like there are times where
I wish I cared about stuff more in terms
of actually like it's easy to talk about
like oh I feel this very feel that way
but I don't know that either was really
do a lot about it other than having a
conversation about it
but I also don't know that I want to
make that effort I feel like well there
are some things
I feel like I just get enraged about
yeah and I feel like you haven't like
studied up because like I do a lot of
reading during the week on the subway
and I'll just get really angry about at
the time but then when I realized that
you don't or haven't read about them
either I'll just like forget about them
or drop them like what sort like a lot
of the things are just things going on
in the world or my celebrity gossip that
I love dearly like I don't know I can't
think about anything specifically but
usually why I bring things out hold on a
sec we're getting down to the end here
how you doing
Carmela yeah
we're you guys filming stuff out there
for this - or different job
she helped
help ya
I can promote this car if it's Darius
how do you think that what parents
vehicle Jews have affected our
relationship of what would you change I
think probably my parents have so I know
that you get frustrated with the way
that my parents are such that comes
across with her political views I don't
think it's truly like beginning it may
have in some ways affected I don't know
if I would change it this is my mom's
works yeah it hasn't because of the fact
that they believe even all but all for
been in the same room months oh right
yeah
that wasn't bad well it was fine but I
mean the thing is if they lived in the
same town and we had the opportunity for
them to get together every two weeks I
don't know that that would necessarily
be a great thing but I think that in the
capacity that it is now which is they
communicate through us largely and see
each other for you know our wedding and
important events and that sort of thing
I think everyone will be cool
who sacrifices more in our relationship
and why I mean I think just objectively
you've made more sacrifices than I have
a necessity in that when we've been
together you know for a year and a half
long distance and I was here just by the
nature of the situation I didn't have
the flexibility to say all right well
I'm going to come to you although to me
so you know I think that is the
number-one thing the fact that you were
willing to leave replaced you live
literally your entire life to being an
absolutely new environment I don't think
I can really equal that in any way but I
think that I try to do a good job of I
guess maybe smaller things or at least
listening to you or listening to your
point of view on stuff when there's
something that's more important to you
or something that would help Plagueis
alleviate some of the loneliness or what
but no I mean when wouldn't the
situation presented itself to move to
where we are on Bay Ridge now and
initially when you brought it up I was
very I don't say dismiss it but I was
very insistent that I wanted to stay in
Astoria because I liked it and I was
comfortable there and I knew people you
know I was friends with come to their
level but but I think that when I took a
step back and realized what you were
asking of me versus what I had asked of
you it wasn't even close so for me to
say like no you have to live in the city
but also the one part of the one borough
that I
it would have been really unreasonable
and so when things like that come up or
even I mean we joke about the idea of
getting a dog or something I've got the
guy I understand that the reality of the
situation is that I don't necessarily
have a ton of friends that I see often
but all of my family and friends are
much closer to me than yours are to you
and I know that that's really hard and
so even though I never imagined getting
a dog how you when something like that
comes up I don't just think of it that's
black and white like do I want a dog
doing that one
it's what would it mean to you and would
it be something that would like improve
your quality of life quite obviously and
happiness because of the fact that I've
had to ask a lot of people I think it is
like an even sacrificing obviously on
that at the beginning moving down here
was similarly a lot and I need you a lot
of my friends and especially like my
family probably even still to this day
some of my pen looks like why you why
did you move to New York I stood and
kept that with you and know that I love
you and that we're getting married to
get all the bad stuff from like moving
to New York
when clearly I'm so in love with the
idea of Maine seems like there's crazy
idea like oh yeah you wouldn't you
wouldn't have moved I mean they're
planning actually there's plenty people
who live in Maine and always want to
live the city of theirs so they went to
Boston to New York whatever but they're
like that's not it's right but that's
you envision for yourself yeah anything
happen that we say would have been
easier definitely I was gonna go there
anyways so go deal with this guy but I
don't think that I don't think you want
to pay that sacrifice if what we had was
wasn't worth because that's a huge thing
to do yeah and I think that at the
beginning way of beginning we both
sacrificed a lot like all those trips
driving to each other in what was ours
are mega buses mega bus yeah I mean
that's the certainly for the first year
and a half it was a lot of sacrifice
both ways in terms of just literally the
logistics of it you know to make it work
to see each other at least once a month
which is what we tried to do that meant
that you or I we're going to have to
drive or take a series of buses eight
hours to see each other and I think that
from the beginning was the reflection of
the fact that what we had going out was
worth all that effort because we would
have been insane to go through that if
it was just for something like casual
sort of thing
if you have a daughter what do you hope
will be different for her in the future
as a woman
I hope that if I have a daughter that
chelonian have to think about the fact
that she would be different from son if
that makes sense yeah
she wouldn't even have to think about
the fact that being a Gender Studies
major would be different than being a
pre-law student that she would have to
think about meeting 75 cents on the
dollar to like stupid things like that
that people bring up every time they
think about gender disability that's a
big it's a big deal and I really hope
that that type of thing is something
that she never even has to think about
yeah like she could just grow up and do
whatever the hell she wants and not have
to think about who she wants to do it
what patterns you wants to use what
religion she wants to be if she wants to
you know go to college or not go to
college whatever like I think that's
like my biggest goal it's just to allow
my daughter's son whatever genders child
I have just allowing them to really be
whoever they wanted me because I think
that if you don't and I think a little
bit of this was on me and I luckily grew
the other way but I see and I I saw a
lot of kids that grew into a very
horrible like militaristic and
uneducated version of a person because
they were told what they were supposed
to be I think that that isn't healthy
and so I'm just hoping to not tell
anyone what to do other than keep them
safe yeah yeah
what you hope I've learned from you
today both of us well I mean again I
think we have a pretty transparent
relationship and so I don't know that I
necessarily came into tonight thinking
that I was gonna have some sort of you
know bombshell discovery about something
that you and I had done
but I hope that it's apparent to you
that these are things that I think about
even if I don't localize that verbalize
that you know that if you ever feel like
I'm not conscious of the sacrifices that
you've made or I'm not aware of the
things that are important to you or the
things that you hope for us in the
future that that's something that I'm
kind of always thinking about even if
I'm not specifically talking about it or
thinking about it that whole which I
hope that you know that but you know
it's not something that we always say
like all right well for the next 15
minutes let's talk about our future it's
just stuff that we've kind of brought up
at various times and then three plus
years we've been together I didn't know
I could stare at you for this long now I
feel like we don't really talk that much
about political things like I think when
we finally get to spend time together
because it seems not like Rare but like
kind of opportunity sort of just spend
that time together catch up on the
things that happen in the day and don't
really want to get weighed down by
political things or like when I because
I kind of get worked up because I just
don't like when people
and so I guess it was nice getting to
hear you you know talk a little bit
about some of your opinions about
side-eye I think I started realized that
we do agree on them nothing in the class
we agree but I think we actually agree a
lot more than I thought that yeah I mean
I kind of wonder how people have strong
relationships when they don't agree on
like fundamental things you know I was
worried going into this that we were and
I like disagree on political things like
I was the ring there are some things
that we that we do disagree on that I
think if you mean that we were just whoa
that's like a huge bombshell I'm like
didn't know you loved Trump today like
that would have been like a big thing I
would have learned but you know I think
that a lot of this stuff that we on the
basilar related group all right
do you think I'd make a good president
or political leader here Obama
impression on us I don't know honey
honestly I'm sorry listen uh yeah I
think that you like pleasing a lot of
people and that's a good thing but you
also don't like letting people down and
I think that to be a leader
unfortunately I have to let at least 50%
or 49% of people check so you may well
your dream job that way no I literally
agree I think I mean up still a kind of
playful Arabic I find that that one
person doesn't like me I'm very
flustered I know and so we still know
exactly who that person was it didn't
like that one show three years ago I
don't know yeah I don't think I have the
stomach for any that stuff I think that
I'm also a very I try to be a very moral
person in the sense that if I've done
something that I feel like is wrong or
slated somebody I it really bothers me
yeah why do you love me so many reasons
I love you because everything has always
been really really easy it's been
everything about us is what people say
doesn't exist when people talk about
what an ideal relationship is it doesn't
mean that you have created 100% all the
time on every single thing you talk
about but it's having that perfect
perfect mixture of friendship with
attraction with respect for somebody and
I think that's in our entire
relationship as angers have been each
other and
time about big things whether it was you
being willing to move here or whether or
not think you're gonna work out there
was never a time that we cursed at each
other or said things that we can take
back and I think that that has laid the
groundwork for a really awesome life
together
and I think that it's just a level of
comfort than I have with you that I
haven't had with anybody else and that's
why even when we think about the future
none of that scares me because I know
that as long as you and I are doing all
that stuff together it's gonna be fine
yeah Cheers have any question any other
questions I popped up for that you want
to ask each other you're worried that I
cannot respond to that answer for all
the same reasons at one plus one